(Beverley:)Barry, stop.
(Leonard:)Seriously, Barry, stop.
(Raj:)And it was Gandhi who said,
“Live as if you were to
“die tomorrow.
“Learn as if you were to live
forever.”
(Sheldon:)And it was Sheldon Cooper who
said “Let's speed this up.
A lot of people want to talk”"
(Leslie:)Uh, in the past, I would've said
something obnoxious,
like, “Happy birthday, dumbass”.
(Leslie:)But I'm not gonna do it.
(Leslie:)You and I have both grown a lot,
(Leslie:)and it's just so nice
to see you all again.
(Amy:)So...
(Leslie:)happy birthday, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Oh, now, you know I hate change.
Say it.
Happy birthday, dumbass!
(cheering)
(Adam:)Happy birthday, young man.
(Adam:)And if any of you have enjoyed
seeing me here today,
(Adam:)I'm also available
for Comic-Cons,
(Adam:)bachelor parties,
bar mitzvahs...
(Bernadette:)I can't think of anything to say
that hasn't already been said.
(Bernadette:)So, here's to you, Sheldon.